
 │█ ▌                  ▌█│         █     █
│█ ▌     Dye Assist     ▌█│       █ █   █ █
 │█ ▌                  ▌█│
                                      ▼       
                                █    █ █    █
                                 ▀▄▄▀   ▀▄▄▀

■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■

╔════════════╗
║Hotkey Setup║
╚════════════╝

► {Delete}: Toggles RGB Checker 
► {PgUp}: Saves a mouse coordinate
► {PgDn}: Moves mouse to saved coordinate
► {Directional Keys}: Moves mouse one pixel at a time
		      (Hold down to keep moving)
► {End}: Terminates Program

■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■

╔══════════╗
║How to Use║
╚══════════╝


► Using RGB Checker

	~ Info: In Vindictus, you cannot hover your mouse over an item
		and then check it's RGB value, so the only way to to it
		is to use photo-editing software to check the value.
	
		* Move your mouse over the item you would like to check
		* Press {Delete} and the game will be tabbed out while
		  RGB values are displayed
		* To stop checking the values, press {Delete} again

► Dye Ampoule Assist

	~ Info: This tool will allow you to be more precise using the
		keyboard rather than dragging your mouse to pick colors
		in a dye ampoule

		* Open the dye ampoule UI by clicking on the unused dye
		* Use the directional keys (ex: ← ↑ ↓ →) inside of the UI
		* To save a coordinate so you can test others, press {PgUp}
		* To return to the coordinate you saved, press {PgDn}


■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■

╔═════╗
║Notes║
╚═════╝

► Be sure to exit the program by pressing {End} before returning to Vindictus
  or the bound keys will not function properly in the game.
